PAMELA SARFO

Telephone: 204-922-3996

Email: Akosuasarfo75@gmail.com

Link or QR code to my E-portfolio



https://pamelasarfo.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Confident in ability to deliver lessons that engage students. I have experience in teaching Math, Science, Coding, Art and Physics in a wide range of classroom settings. I have experience in tutoring middle and high school students.

Integrity is my hallmark keen in working and learning from others.

SKILLS

- Good listener
- Hardworking
- Focused
- Compassionate
- Typing
- Accuracy

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Student Teacher at Earl Oxford School, Brandon-Manitoba (March 2021- May 2021)
- Substitute Teacher for Brandon School Division (November 2020 to Date)
- Student Teacher at River Heights School, Brandon, Manitoba (September 2020-December 2020)
- Student Teacher at Virden Collegiate Institute, Virden, Manitoba (March 2020)
- Student Teacher at Vincent Massey High School, Brandon, Manitoba (October 2019-December 2019)
- Physics Tutor at Anglican Senior High School, Ghana (2017-2018)

EDUCATION

- **September 2019** –**May 2021** Brandon University, Currently Pursuing the After-degree program in Education (final year student)
- October 2013 June 2017 Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology, Ghana Physics with Biomedical as option

HOBBIES

- Cooking
- Sewing
- Listening to music
- Reading
- Coaching

REFERENCES

• Professor Dr. Kirk Jacqueline

Faculty of Education, Brandon University

Cell: 204-730-0164 (preferred text)

Office phone: 204-571-8576 Email: kirkj@brandonu.ca

• Rick Stallard

Cell: 204-761-7932

Email: Stallard.r@outlook.com

• Dr. Mike Nantais

Faculty of Education, Brandon University

Cell: 204-727-9619

Email: nantaism@brandonu.ca